<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Todo-02</string>
    <string name="t1">Feasibility study on online Vegetable marketing</string>
    <string name="t3">The global economy and the organization from different parts of the world have witnessed tremen-
dous changes in the last three decades with technological advancement in online marketing. Visit This Page online
        vegetable marketing has driven the ideas of traditional marketing to the advanced system.\n\n
        Visit this page for more info <a href="www.facebook.com">www.google.com</a>
        The new application and ideas are already available to the general public but there is much space to
learn and keep on upgrading. The idea of online marketing is instantly flourishing over the world
        fulfilling the basic needs of the people.\n \n The system of online marketing was launched within Bhutan
from the past few years and it is overwhelming contributing in the living standard of the people
in Bhutan. Over the time, the demand for the online application system is growing in the country.\n \n
where all citizens are into the advanced system with the new features. On the other hand such
applications system are able to solve the problem of unemployed youths in the country.
In online marketing, people can advertise and reserve the product over the internet and get the
required product at the quick instant of time. This application system is fast and efficient as it
provides detailed information on the vegetables, services and offers of the seller.\n\nMoreover in such
type of marketing the time of the seller, as well as the time of the customer is saved as both the seller
and customer do not have to meet face to face in the market. This business provides a platform for
the customer to reserve the vegetables and the seller to advertise the vegetable from any place at
particular instant of time within the range of the market.\n\n
On believing the concept and fact of online vegetable marketing, the team builds the curiosity to
learn and see the feasibility of online vegetable marketing in Mongar. In Mongar, every weekend
people have to gather in the vegetable market and to do the necessary shopping for vegetables for
            the rest of the days.\n\n In this situation, it becomes hard for people of Mongar to get vegetables of
the right diet as many people rush to get vegetables at once.\n\n The time limit for buyers and sellers
to do market is very less as there are many customers in Mongar District. \nMore importantly due
to huge gathering every weekend there is also a high risk of spreading diseases. However, to sell
their vegetable on market, farmers have to store their products in stock which spoils the quality
and freshness of vegetables, as a result, it deteriorates the price of vegetables.\n\n

Due to such problems as mentioned above, our team is going to find weather there is a need for
online vegetable marketing in Mongar. Online vegetable marketing would ease marketing strategy
and would solve the problems of spreading diseases in a community and time consumption for mar-
keting would be reduced for both sellers and buyers.\n\n So based on these statements the team would
be researching the feasibility of an online vegetable market in Mongar.</string>
</resources>